好吧  这是什么
So, now, what is this, now?
咯咯叫的扭扭虫
Googlie Worm. Ha-ha-ha.
那这个呢
And this?
呵呵傻笑的萤火虫
Glow Pop Jiggly Jam.
好好玩喔
Bait is so funny.
嗨  这是什么
Hey, um, what's this?
去年剩的一块三明治
Oh, a hunk of sandwich from last year.
哦  盖勒钓到了  看来是条大鱼  哦  哦
Oh, Geller's got one hooked. Oh! Looks like a big one. Oh! Oh!
经典的人鱼大战…
It's the classic struggle between man...
有人把台灯撞到了
Someone knocked over a lamp.
嗨  你们知道  这次去钓鱼最棒的是…
Hey, you know what's gonna be great about the fishing trip?
老爸把我从湖中央救出来  问我 "乔伊  你这辈子怎么办呀"
When my dad gives me that, "Joey, what are you doing with your life?" stuff...
我可以说  我要跟却尔登希斯顿演电影
...I can say, "Well, I'm doing a movie with Charlton Heston, Dad.
你这辈子呢
What are you doing with your life?" Aw.
太棒了
Great!
别因为我出来就不继续开心了
You don't have to stop having fun just because I'm here.
凯西没有背叛你们
Kathy didn't cheat on all of you.
好吧  除了你
Well, except you.
乔伊  你不该丢下钱德
Hey, Joey, I don't think you should leave Chandler alone.
我的意思是  他跟凯西才分手两天
I mean it's only been two days since he broke up with Kathy.
下周再去钓鱼吧
Maybe you can go fishing next week.
可是  我现在帮不上忙  他还穿着运动裤
Look, There's nothing I can do right now. He's still in his sweatpants.
现在是第一阶段
That's only phase one.
我第二阶段就会回来的  我从不错过第二阶段
You know? I'll be back for phase two. I would never miss phase two.
什么第二阶段
What's phase two?
喝的烂醉  去看脱衣舞
Getting drunk and going to a strip club.
看脱衣舞对他有什么帮助
How does going to a strip club make him better?
那里有好多裸女
There are naked ladies there.
而且还可以帮他到达第三阶段  对别的女人产生性幻想
It helps him get to phase three, picturing yourself with other women.
那个阶段也有裸女  对
There are naked ladies there too. Yeah.
让我清静一下  好吗
Would you give me one minute, please?
老友记  第四季  第14集  乔伊臭臭的一天
Friends S04E14  The One With Joey's Dirty Day
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
这跟你上星期给我挑的夹克外套配吗
So these will match the jacket you picked out for me last week?
很好嘛
There we go.
就是这样
There it is.
你知道还缺什么嘛  知道
Oh, you know what I need? Yeah?
手套  棕色的皮手套  好
Gloves. Brown leather dress gloves. Oh, okay.
好吧  让我看看  这只手是大号
Uh, well, let's see. You're about a... Well, this one is large. Ha, ha.
这只手
And, uh, this one...
也是大号  对
Also a large? Yeah. Okay.
好  两只大号的手套马上就来
Yeah. Two larges coming right up. Ha, ha.
瑞秋  耽误你下  好
Rachel, could I have a moment? Yes.
你瞧  我的侄女从伦敦来玩
I was wondering, my niece, you see, is in town from London.
其实是什罗普郡  说来唐突  不过
Uh-huh. Shropshire, really, but you know.
她跟你差不多大
She's about your age, I'd say.
总之  我这里碰巧有歌剧《蝙蝠》的票
Anyway, I have tickets for the opera. Die Fledermaus.
不知道你今晚能不能陪她去看呢
and I was wondering if you would keep her company this evening.
当然可以了  没问题  太好了
Sure. You got it. Oh, good.
算我一份  我和《蝙蝠》  太棒了  不过
Count me in. Me, Fledermaus. Great. I really
好  谢谢  谢谢你  太感谢你了
Oh, yes, of course. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you so very much.
好了么
So?
什么
So...
手套  对喔  对不起  我马上去拿
Gloves? Oh, right. Sorry, I'll be right back.
其实  我该走了
Actually, you know what? I gotta take off.
不过  不知道你今晚有空么
But I was curious, do you have any plans for tonight?
有  当然有了
No, nothing.
我投资的夜总会今晚开业  你想去看看么
I invested in this night-club and it's opening tonight, Would you like to come?
当然了  那太好了
Yeah, that would be great.
你喜欢性虐待的主题吧
You're into hard-core S and M, right?
应该  我  开玩笑的
Well, I guess. I'm kidding.
我会先到  会把你列为贵宾  进来找我
I'm gonna get there early, but I'm going to put you on the V.I.P list, Look for me.
好  没问题  晚上见
Yeah. Great. You betcha. I'll see you tonight.
好  好
Okay. Okay.
我差点忘了给你票  是吧  什么
I almost forgot the tickets, didn't I? What?
你和艾蜜莉  今晚  去看《蝙蝠》
For you and Emily. Tonight. Die Fledermaus.
对  是的
Oh. Oh, right.
你一定会喜欢  世界三大男高音去了两个
I think you'll like it. It has two of the Three Tenors.
好耶
Okay.
真不敢相信  凯西居然会这么对我  我真的把她当作自己今生唯一的伴侣
Y'know,I can't believe Kathy did this to me. I really thought that she was the one.
算了  告诉你们
Well, I'll tell you what.
从现在开始  我再也不会离开这张椅子了
From now on, I am not getting out of this chair, ever.
从现在开始  这椅子就是我的唯一
Okay? From now on, this chair is the one.
你们知道还有什么  我的运动裤
You know what else is the one? My sweat pants.
别这样  老兄  把裤子脱下来好么
Come on, man, just take the sweats off, okay?
快脱吧  我们来玩一玩
Just take them off and we'll have some fun.
嘿  嗨
Hey. Hi.
钓到大鱼了吗  天呀  你们肯定不信
Did you catch any big fish? Oh, my God, you guys have no idea.
哦  天呀  你好臭啊
Oh, wow. Oh, my God, you stink.
搞什么呢
Oh, are you kidding?
我待在湖上  整整三天没洗澡
Yeah, three days on the lake without a shower.
而且  还掉进一个装鱼饵的桶里了
Plus, I fell into that big tub of worms at the bait stand.
嗨  他怎么样了
Hey, how's he doing?
他已经两天没离开过那张椅子了
He hasn't gotten out of that chair in two days.
嗨  兄弟  你还好吗
Ahem. Hey, buddy, how's it going?
看见了么  好兄弟回家就没事了
You see that? He just needed his pal to come home.
好了  我得去背台词了
All right, uh, I gotta go memorize my lines.
明天一早  要和却尔登希斯顿演戏
Me and Charlton Heston, bright and early tomorrow, baby.
好耶  好耶
Yeah. Yeah.
嘿   嘿
Hey. Hey.
嘿   摩妮卡
Hey. Hey, Monica.
怎么了
Uh-oh. What's the matter? Oh...
约书亚约我今晚去一家刚开业的高级夜总会
Joshua invited me to this fancy club opening tonight.
可我已经答应沃森先生
But I already told Mr. Waltham...
带他的侄女去看什么破歌剧
...that I would take his niece to the dumb old opera.
唉  怎么办呢
So, what are you gonna do?
我也不知道  亲爱的  不行  帮帮我
I don't know, sweetie. No. Help me.
我不行  我要上班  菲比
I can't. I have to work. Phoebe?
我倒是很想  可我晚上有妊娠反应
I would, but I get my morning sickness in the evening.
除非  她想整晚上都过不安生
Ooh, no, unless she wants to spend the night holding my hair back for me.
拜托  天哪  你们  我一定要去见约书亚
Ugh. Gosh, you guys, come on. This is... I have to meet Joshua.
这是唯一的机会  让他看看有趣的瑞秋
This is my one chance for him to see the fun Rachel.
也许 他会想 "要是瑞秋是我老婆该多好呀"
You know, the "Wouldn't it be great if she were my wife?" Rachel.
算了  乔伊和钱德回来了吗
Ohh, all right! Are Joey and Chandler back?
没有  钱德还在第一阶段  乔伊身上的味道你总该闻见了吧
Oh, Chandler's still in phase one, and Joey's that thing you smell.
嗨
Hi.
Hi!
所以…
So?
不要
No.
拜托啦
Oh, come on.
应该是她  等下  等下  罗斯  拜托啦
I think she's here. No, wait, wait, wait. Ross, please?
你要我带一个不认识的女生  去看歌剧
You want me to take some girl I've never met to the opera...
好让你去夜总会  跟某个男人打情骂俏
...so you can go to a club and flirt with some guy?
真难决定啊
Hmm. Yeah, that is a toughie.
她在四处张望
Oh, she's looking down the hall.
她在看我
Oh! She looked right at me.
等等  这洞从外面看不进来  对吧
Oh, wait, you can't see people through that little hole, can you?
你好啊
Hello.
你好
Hello? Aah!
我马上出来  罗斯  拜托啦  帮帮忙吧
Oh, I'll be right there. Okay, Ross, please. Come on.
我以为我们之间的事都过去了
I thought we had moved on.
我以为我们可以彼此相互祝福了
I thought we'd gotten to a place where we could be happy for each other.
难道只是我这样想么
I mean was that just me?
好吧  我答应你  谢谢你  谢谢你  谢谢你
All right, I'll do it. Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you.
艾蜜莉  是
Emily? Yes.
我是瑞秋葛林  谢天谢地
I'm Rachel Green. Thank goodness.
计划有小小的变动  我晚上没空  所以…
There's been a teeny-teeny change in plans. It turns out that I'm not free tonight. So…
是吗
Really? Heh.
真是太巧了  不是么  我一定是没接到你的电话  虽然我整天都没出门
Well, that's just lovely, isn't it? I must've missed your call, even though I didn't leave the flat all day.
不  其实我  不  不  不  还算好啦
Well, no, I... No, no, no, that's not rude.
我这一路上
It's perfectly in keeping with a trip...
差点儿被你们热狗车撞倒
...where I've already been run down by one of your wiener carts...
在约翰F肯尼迪机场  又被脱衣搜身
...and been strip-searched at John F. Kennedy Airport.
显然  我长得就像
Apparently, I look like someone...
屁股里塞满了可卡因
...who's got a balloon full of cocaine stuffed up their bum.
我-我-我觉得你很漂亮啊
I-I-I think you look great.
再见  很高兴认识你们
Good night. It was very nice to meet you all.
我去追她
I'll get her.
快去  好
Please hurry. Okay.
他们讲话好好玩
Don't you just love the way they talk?
怎么了  踢我了  孩子踢我了
What? It kicked. I think the baby kicked.
天啊  上帝呀  噢
Oh, my God. Ha, ha.
不对  是内裤的松紧带断了
Oh, no, wait. Oh. That was the elastic in my underwear busted.
完了  我睡过头了
Oh, my God. I overslept.
通告是半小时前就要到场的  我得赶快
I was supposed to be on the set a half an hour ago. I gotta get out of here.
你不能这样出去吧  你好臭
What? Joey, you can't go like that. You stink.
没办法啊  我还没洗澡就睡着了  现在没时间了
Look, I know I feel asleep before I could shower and now I don't have time!
才十条街  用跑的还来得及
They're 10 blocks away. If I run, I can make it.
那是  跑10个街区  你会更臭了
Yeah, run 10 blocks. That'll help the smell.
慢一点  算了  快跑
Hey. Whoa! Slow down. No, keep moving. Whoa.
昨晚怎么样啊  我没见到约书亚
So how did it go with Joshua last night? Oh. Well, I didn't see Joshua.
但我揍了一个女生一拳
But I did punch a girl in the face.
什么   为什么
What? Why?
昨晚真的很倒楣   倾盆大雨
The whole night was horrible. It was pouring rain.
到了现场  名单上没有瑞秋葛林  只有瑞秋葛皮
and when I got there, there was no Rachel Green on the list, but there was a Rachel Greep.
那你见到她了么
Oh. So did you get to meet her?
没有  根本没这个人  但有个女生听到了
No, there is no Rachel Greep. But then this other girl overheard us.
大声嚷嚷 "我就是瑞秋葛皮  我就是"  结果她就进去了
And she was all, "I'm Rachel Greep, I'm Rachel Greep," and he let her in.
然后你就朝她脸上打了一拳  没有  她已经进去了
So you hit her in the face? No, she was already in.
不过后面有个肥婆想偷我的伞
But then this big bitch behind me tried to steal my umbrella...
被我一拳揍在脸上
...so I clocked her.
我真不敢相信
Ugh. I can't believe this.
我只是想在下班后  跟约书亚相处一下
All I wanted was just a few hours outside of work to see Joshua...
好让他有机会爱上我
...so that he could go ahead and start falling in love with me.
菲比
Aw. Pheebs.
亲爱的  那是你的名字
Honey, that's your name.
我以为那是我们之间的昵称
That's short for Phoebe? I thought that's what we called each other.
你穿上裤子了  没错
Hey, you're wearing pants. That's right.
男人们都到哪里去了  我准备好了 要买醉看脱衣舞
Where are the guys? I'm ready to get drunk and see strippers.
才早上9点半  他们那里有自助早餐的
It's 9:30 in the morning. They got a breakfast buffet.
喂  罗斯  让我跟他说
Hello? Oh, hey, Ross. Ooh. Let me talk to him.
天哪
Oh, my God.
我能不能  等等  什么
Can't I just...? Shh. Wait, what?
我的电话  她还嘘我  别吵啦
It's my phone and she's shush... Shh. Please.
他说什么
What's he saying?
他跟艾蜜莉在佛蒙特的一个旅馆
He's with Emily at a bed and breakfast in Vermont.
什么  哦  天哪
What? Oh, my God.
艾蜜莉是谁  不会吧
What? Who the hell is Emily? Noooo!!
他们在佛蒙特  怎么会这样
They're in Vermont? How did this happen?
嗷
Ow.
他怎么会跟那个巫婆去佛蒙特
How—How did he end up in Vermont with that awful witch?
也许她没有一直打他吧
Maybe she doesn't hit him all the time.
我们见到她时…
When we first met her...
她湿透了  连脚都是湿的
...she was soaking, her feet were wet.
谁能比她更可怜
Who wouldn't be miserable?
是真的  我给她换了双鞋后  她完全变了个人
I'm telling you when I got her into a dry pair of shoes, she was a totally different person.
罗斯  快来  外面有只驯鹿在吃果园的水果
Ross, come quickly. There's a deer outside eating fruit from the orchard.
我要挂了  外面有只驯鹿在吃果园的水果
I gotta go! There's a deer outside eating fruit from the orchard!
他挂了  外面有只驯鹿在吃果园的水果
He had to go, there's a deer just outside eating fruit from the orchard.
真想不通   她那么讨厌
I don't get this. She was horrible.
我要去站在那边
Okay, I'm gonna go stand over there.
你干嘛这么在乎  我才不在乎
Why do you care so much, anyway? I don't care.
我只是有点儿心烦  我跟约书亚没任何进展
You know what? I'm just upset that I'm getting nowhere with Joshua.
但哪有人刚认识  就跑去佛蒙特鬼混的
Know what? Still, you do not just meet someone and go flitting off to Vermont.
你和贝瑞一认识就飞到维尔去了
Well, when you first met Barry, you flitted off to Vail.
你能不能偶尔有一次  不要记得这些琐碎小事
Ugh. You know, could you just for once not remember every little thing?
你知道他什么时候回来么
So, you know, when's he getting back?
几天后吧  我就知道会这样
A couple of days. Know what? I knew something like this was gonna happen.
你干什么
What are you doing?
钱德  你不能让阶段倒流
Chandler. You can't just go back a phase.
可以  你说的是时间  你不能让时光倒流
Yes, you can. You're thinking about time. You can't go back in time.
你为什么不  不继续你的第二阶段呢
Why don't you just...? Why don't you do your phase-two strip-club thing with us?
对呀  来吧  我们可以当男生  不  你们不行
Yeah, come on, we can be guys. Heh. No, you can't.
怎么了  不就是扮男的嘛  也许我们本来就想当
Come on, let us be guys. Maybe we wanna be guys.
你们才不会想当男的
You don't wanna be guys.
男人浑身是毛  而且短命
You'd be all hairy and you wouldn't live as long.
你  你
You know, you...
你别再唧唧歪歪了  把运动裤脱了
Would you just stop being such a wuss and get those off?
跟我们去看裸女跳舞
And you come with us and watch naked girls dance around.
好
Okay.
对不起
I'm sorry.
（银杯片厂）
我是乔伊崔比亚尼  我来了 我来了
Hey, Joey Tribbiani. I'm here, I'm here.
别急  来得及  进度有点落后
Calm down, we got time. We're running a little late.
准备好了
All set.
你看  却尔登希斯顿在嚼甘草
Look at that. Charlton Heston eating a licorice whip.
他很爱嚼甘草  我从没见过他…
Yeah, he loves them. I've never seen him with...
哇  这儿怎么了  什么东西这么臭
Whoa. Yeah. What the hell is that? What smells so bad?
是你
You. Oh.
难怪你会这么想  你知道实际上我怎么想的吗
I could see why you would think that. But actually, you know who I think it is?
你么  不  是希斯顿
You? No, no. It's Heston.
什么  就是他身上的臭
What? The man reeks.
闻起来像是去钓了三天的鱼  现在还嚼甘草
Smells like he went on a three-day fishing trip and then ate licorice. Ick.
不可能是他呀
There's no way he smells.
只有他的休息室有浴室
He's the only one around here with a shower in his dressing room.
真的  浴室  嗯  是哪间
Really? A shower, huh? And, uh, which room might that be?
门口有写 "希斯顿"的那间
The one with "Heston" on it.
有意思
Interesting.
我换了零钞  你要不要去放到她的小裤裤里啊
Hey. I got some ones. You wanna put them in her panties?
不用了  谢谢  老妈
No, thanks, Mom.
啊  哦  别  那个
Oh. No. Um, hi. That, that.
抱歉  你得把烟掐掉  我怀孕了
You have to put that out because I'm pregnant, so...
也许你和你的孩子应该去别家脱衣舞夜总会了
Well, maybe you and your baby ought to go to another strip club.
呵-呵  这不是我的孩子  呵-呵-呵
Heh, heh. It's not my baby. Heh, heh.
很好  很好
Very good. Yes. That was so good.
太棒了  我喜欢  很火辣
Really, really enjoyed it. Very exotic.
我查过留言  约书亚没打来过
Well, I just checked our messages, and Joshua didn't call.
我还以为我没去他的夜总会  他会担心呢
I mean you'd think he'd be worried about me not showing up at his club.
更糟的是  罗斯还在佛蒙特风流快活
Ugh. And you know what makes it worse? Ross is all happy in Vermont.
拜托  你在看脱衣舞啊
Come on, look where you are.
麻烦给我们每人一杯鸡尾酒  别忘了  我还要个处男
When you get a sec, another round of daiquiris.Remember, virgin for me, please.
记得提醒我  问那个帅哥的名字
Oh, and don't let me leave without getting the name of that carpet guy.
拜托
Oh, come on.
算了  我这就回家给凯西打电话
You know what? I'm just gonna go home and call Kathy.
如果有用的话  不  我只是试试
Well, if you think it'll help. No. That was a test.
再过几小时  我就会烂醉如泥  想打给凯西
In a couple hours, I'm gonna get drunk and wanna call Kathy...
你们得阻止我呀
...and you have to stop me.
然后我醉的一塌糊涂了  说不定还会给珍妮丝打电话
Then I'm gonna be so drunk, I'm gonna wanna call Janice.
你是该打  她好吗
You should. How is she? Oh!
我想有人肯定会觉得表演还不够过瘾
I think somebody needs another lap dance.
哈罗  谁在里面
Hello? Who's in there?
你好吗
How you doing?
你到底是谁
Who in the hell are you?
我说寇克道格拉斯  你不会信吧
Uh, guess you wouldn't believe me if I said I was Kirk Douglas, huh?
把裤子穿上  我好踢你屁股
Put some pants on, kid, so I can kick your butt.
不  等等  你有所不知
No, no, no, wait. You don't understand.
我是个演员
You see, I'm an actor.
乔伊崔比亚尼  今天跟你有一场戏
Joey Tribbiani. I'm doing a scene with you today.
但是我很臭（演得很烂）
And, well, I stink.
你有演这部片  对  对
You're in this picture? Yeah, yeah.
我演不肯跟你合作的警察  因为你的倔脾气
I'm one of the cops who won't work with you because you're a loose cannon.
总之  我很抱歉  但我真的很臭（演得很烂）
Anyway, look, I'm really sorry, but I just... I stink.
乔伊  是吧  对
Joey, right? Yeah.
每个演员或多或少…
Every actor, one time or another... Ah.
都会觉得自己很臭
Every actor thinks he stinks.
连劳伦斯奥立佛  有时也会这么想
Even Laurence Olivier sometimes thought he stank.
劳勃瑞福甚至都不敢正眼瞧自个儿  不  不  不  你没明白我
Bob Redford won't even watch himself. No, no, no, you don't understand.
听我说  是  好的
Listen to me. No... Yeah.
我就不相信任何一个称职的演员
I don't know one actor worth his salt...
在演艺生涯中都不曾说过 "天哪  我真的太臭了"
...who one time in his career didn't say, "God, I stink."
我刚拍完一场戏  第一镜  我演得烂透了
Hell, I just did a scene out there. First take, I stunk the place up.
重要的是你要记住
But the important thing that you must remember...
不管你认为自己有多臭
...no matter how badly you think you stink...
永远也别闯到我的更衣室来  用我的淋浴
...you must never, ever bust into my dressing room and use my shower.
听明白了么
Do you understand me?
是的  是的  我这就  慢着
Yes, sir. Yes, sir. I'm very sorry. Wait a minute.
把裤子带走  是
Take your pants. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
我们在脱衣舞夜总会表现得还好吧  是的  好得很
So we did okay at the strip club, right? Oh, yeah. That was great.
谢谢你们  你们让最性感的服务生
Thanks to you, the hottest cocktail waitress there is quitting...
都想辞职去教三年级了
...to teach the third grade.
真不敢相信  他居然还没打来
I can't believe it. He still hasn't called.
谁  约许  不  是约书亚
Who, Josh? It's "Joshua."
他不喜欢约许  是我不喜欢
What, he doesn't like "Josh"? No, I don't.
好吧  我要把运动裤换回来
All right. Well, I'm gonna put my sweats back on.
不要啦  等一下  你说得对  你是对的
Oh no! wait. You know what? You were right, you were right.
我们扮不好男人  你知道为什么吗
We really weren't great at being guys. But do you know why?
因为我们是女人
Because we're girls.
所以呢  你知道女生最擅长什么吗
Yeah. Do you know what girls are good at?
跳脱衣舞
Stripping.
不  是倾听  坐下来
No, listening. Sit.
也许只要你说出来  或许就没事了
You know, maybe it would really, really help if you would just talk.
是啊  说吧  你的心里在想什么
Yeah, come on. What's going on in there?
当然了  你想哭也没关系
And you know, if you wanna cry, that's okay too.
好了  我要请你们都离开
Okay, look, I'm gonna have to ask you all to leave.
别这样嘛  钱德
Come on, Chandler.
算了  我们试过了  第三阶段没希望了
Look, forget it. We tried, but phase three is a lost cause.
那些脱衣女郎都野性十足
Okay? Those strippers were insanely hot...
可我就是没法产生性幻想
...and I couldn't picture myself with any of them.
她们真的很漂亮  不是么
They really were pretty, weren't they? Oh.
我最喜欢那个救火笼驾驶员  糖糖
I really liked that fighter pilot one. Oh, Candy?
她火花四射  对啊
Oh, she was so spunky. Yeah.
要是我想和女人在一起的话…
You know, I think if I were gonna be with a woman...
我会选蜜雪充那型娇小的
...it'd be with someone like Michelle.
她简直太  太姣美了
She was... Oh, she was just so petite.
是么  我到没这么想  如果是我  我会选香姐
See, I don't know. For me, it would have to be Chantal.
没错  香姐  香姐
Oh, Chantal, yeah. Chantal.
对啊  哦  天哪…
You know? Oh, my God. The... Oh.
她的皮肤好光滑呀
She had the smoothest skin.
我塞钱给她时手擦过她的大腿… 第三阶段
I mean, when I stuck that dollar bill in her G-string and grazed her thigh...Phase three!
我终于进入第三阶段了
I just achieved phase three!
真的
Really?
我现在满脑子想像你们跟她们在一起
I am totally picturing you with all those women.
那不是第三阶段  不过  我也在场
That's not phase three. Well, I'm there too.
我们都在一起像个团队吗  别说了  我快疯了
Well, are we all together? Like in a group? Stop it, you're killing me.
我进入第四阶段了
I think I just moved on to phase four.
那是什么  我什么关系都不想要了
Oh, what is that? What is that? Where I don't want a relationship ever.
只想和那些脱衣女郎还有我的朋友们做爱
I just wanna have sex with strippers and my friends.
来嘛  让我看看你的笑脸
Come on. Let me see that smile.
我高兴不起来
I don't wanna.
拜托啦
Please?
我想去看脱衣舞嘛
I wanted to go to the strip club.
我知道  你有的是机会  好吧
I know, You're gonna have plenty of chances, okay?
外面有成千上万的女人等着我呢
There are thousands of women out there who are just waiting to screw me over.
是的  好吧
Yeah, all right.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
你在佛蒙特玩得好吗
Hey. Ooh, how was Vermont?
艾蜜莉真是难以置信
Emily is incredible.
我是说好得无法形容
I mean, there are no words to describe her.
整个周末就像一场梦
The whole weekend was like a dream.
还有你  瑞秋  嘿   噢   嘿
Oh. And you. Rach. Hey. Oh, hey.
你说得太对了  什么
You were so right. What?
你说我们总算到了一个
What you said about us finally being in a place...
可以彼此祝福的阶段
...where we could really be happy for each other.
我是说  我
Hmm. I mean, I...
我得承认  开始并没有这样想
I admit, I wasn't quite there. Mm-hm.
因为一想到你和那个叫约许…
You know, I mean, the thought of you and that Josh guy...
约书亚  约书亚  在夜总会里
"Joshua." Joshua guy at that club...
跳舞狂欢
...dancing, having a good time.
那种感觉有点儿
the thought of it kinda
你懂吗  懂
You know? Yeah.
但现在  我完全想通了
But now, but now, I'm totally there.
我现在和你想法一样
I'm finally where you are.
噢  谢天谢地
Oh, thank goodness.
谢谢你把艾蜜莉介绍给我
Yeah, and thank you for Emily.
没什么  很高兴我能帮上忙
Oh, no problem. I'm so glad I could help, you know?
也为你高兴
I'm happy for you.
我才替你开心
Happy for you.
不  我才替你开心
Oh, no, happy for you.
好吧  女士们  接下来是这样
All right, ladies, here's what we're gonna do.
你帮我脱衣服
You are gonna take off my clothes.
你们两个去拿精油
You two go get the oils.
你就一直兴奋的大叫
And you constantly scream at the top of your voice:
"吾王钱德万岁"  "吾王钱德万岁"
"Chandler's the king! Chandler's the king!"
我  我想跟她在一起  我喜欢她
No, I wanna be with her. I like her.
没问题  大家随意  大家随意
Oh, that's fine. Go with your instincts. Go with your instincts.
等等  我要做什么
Wait, what am I doing again?
专心一点  我随时都会醒来
Would you please pay attention? I could wake up at any moment.
嗨  我是约书亚  我来接瑞秋
Hi, I'm Joshua. I'm here to pick up Rachel.
不  不  不  他不是约书亚
No, no, no, that's not Joshua.
我又没见过他  管他的呢
What do you want from me? I never met the guy.
不好意思  瑞秋  你得走了  我们还有很多事要忙
So anyway, Rachel, I'm sorry you can't stay. The rest of us have a lot of work to do.
你干什么
What are you doing?
好吧  听着  我得醒过来了
All right, listen, I've got to wake up!